me on static in the cathedral screen.
Pixel ghosts whisper what the smiles really mean.
Everybody's talking, everybody's selling dreams,
but the truth leaks out between the broken seams.
The oracle buffering.
Loading, da-da-da-da-loading.
The king says loyalty, but the queen says trust.
The djista says wisdom, while counting your dust.
Everybody's streaming from a beautiful day cell
Watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch
He said that I drink mugwort tea, and it's not even here yet.
Okay, well I'm sorry, I don't know what you're- what the fuck you're drinking, old man.
Okay, listen, mugwort tea or whatever, you're- you're- you're lame as fuck.
That's your argument, I said you drink mugwort tea and that's why you're angry and I'm a liar about you because I said you drink mugwort tea.
Am I am I saying hey Sharon? How are you sweetheart? I know I mean Sharon? I can't take it anymore
And I'm a money for 20s bronze bronze bitch and Christina mods over there
And this hide me in the chat and and pity me off the channel
And so he made like a hundred bucks tonight off of me getting kicked off
So I was like money for 20 just mod me. I'll come back. I'll get kicked off a thousand more times
You know it's a it's a money source for you
Uh, I can't have too many mods. It's a bad thing.
I would say, I never hate one person.
He has brown bitch and Christine Cunt hiding people.
And he doesn't know. I mean, I can't explain it to people enough.
I mean, it's just too retarded for me.
Not to, you know, I feel bad for retarded people now.
With the retards that are not even retarded, that are just retarded.
I mean, it's getting sad.
Oh, I didn't drink mugwort tea.
You liar, oh, you lied to Alexander about me.
I didn't drink tea.
Isn't it frustrating?
I mean, it's like, okay, you didn't drink mugwort tea.
You're drinking distilled whiskey or something like that.
I don't know, your highest fuck is all I know.
I don't know what you were drinking.
You kept talking about mugwort tea.
Right, I mean it's like oh, yeah, and then it's like okay. Well, okay. You want to make some money off me?
I'll make you some money cut me into it
Be friends behind the scenes or something like some kind of like you know
I show a faith that I'm not just some like, you know idiot or whatever. No, it has to be a bronze bitch and Christine
They probably donated five dollars twenty five dollars to give me kicked off and stuff. Oh, they give me the mods
Oh, but I can't because then they get mad. Oh, you want you don't make bronze bitch and Christine mad
Because you see how they treat me.
Oh, psyche, your nails, you're still digging your ass.
Christine, your whole face looks like it's been digging
an ass for a hundred years.
I mean, that's what your face looks like.
Don't talk about my fingernails.
My fingernails look a lot better than your face.
And by the way, they look great.
I mean, it's like, geez.
In Money 420, thanks a lot for the $2 for the clippers.
You know, I don't need them.
And thanks for like not even donating two dollars after you said you would several times and fucking
You got donated like a hundred dollars
But you know, no, you don't have to like spend two seconds like send me two dollars cash out
They said he would send me in front of everybody
No, you can just pretend like you're you're helping me out, right and then make fun of me at the same time
Okay, that's fine. It's fine Sharon. You get it. You get it. I mean, it's like
We these people I mean, I don't know what's wrong. I mean some of these people
Well, oh you platform this person. Oh, but there goes the content
Midnight, right minutes boy. Okay. You got rid of the content grams. Good for you. Yay
I mean, that's what they wanted to do. They would it's gonna get rid of the content. I mean, it's like
I'm not bad content. I'm entertaining. I'm actually a blessing more. I go
I'm actually a blessing. I'm a blessing disguise. I look like a big curse, but I'm a blessing
And it's like, if I talk about you drinking mugwort tea or whatever, just go with it.
I tend to think, yes, it makes you look cooler than you are, probably, grandpa.
Because then you're like, oh, mugwort tea doesn't do anything.
If you're ordering it, it's probably very expensive from a witch, right?
All the good mugwort comes from.
If you order from the right place.
But no, you're like, oh, before it even gets there, oh, it doesn't even work.
Why are you paying money for it?
You're starving for a grub hub of delivery.
Order that instead of a $20 of a mugwort tea at times, okay?
Order a mugwort on your pizza or something like that.
Okay, I'm sorry that I tried to promote you.
You got wine?
Okay, come on up.
I mean, Good Time just pissed the fuck off.
I mean, it's like, oh my gosh.
Now I'm at the stage two with Good Time, Alex.
I'm at stage two with him already.
I mean, you were telling me today,
you're gonna be stage two, where he turns on me.
He's like, you lied to Alexandra.
You said, I drink mugwort tea.
That's what he was literally upset about.
I don't know, he was literally, he hid me from his chat
and says, you're banned.
You said I drank, that was his, he's like,
you're lying about me to Alexandra,
because you said I drank milk or tea.
I'm sorry, I had a nap, I have another half of a heart
lemonade, I'm good, I'm gonna get another drink too.
But yeah.
I mean it was it's absolutely crazy and then the money for 20 thing
I don't know. I made him like 50 bucks today, you know, it's father's day. I'm not having the easiest father's day
I don't need to go on bottom panel have Christine say I'm just like a piece of shit like this disgusting like dirty and
Bad person and then she says I'm a lying lying to Alexander because I said what she said she said Chris
She said um summer was a grifter. I mean she said that's what either played on money on a sorry
I'd say a man show you play that clip, but that shows not around anymore. So
I mean, but geez
Whoo, okay, let me fix my screen too. I'm kind of like I'm I'm in my 80s
My 80s glitching out period right now. Just fix this for you guys
And Alex, I wouldn't lie to you like, like they're saying they're like, they're acting like I'm just like lying to you and stuff, I wouldn't, I wouldn't like, I have my memory of things and I heard Christina the other day say that stuff.
And I am, I just now her good time say that stuff and I called him a pussy and I call him an old fart and whatever. I mean, it's like, because he's like sitting there is so angry.
Hey, we have Alex on the show. Let's welcome Alex.
Hi.
I'm making an appearance. Here I am. I'm alive. I'm turning the camera back off though.
Okay, here we are.
I got nothing done this weekend. I got some stuff done, but nothing I didn't tend it to,
so I'm drinking.
Me too. I have another half-heart lemonade. I wouldn't got a subway. I thought it was a subway sandwich, but it was like something in a tortilla
It was like a battalion sandwich and a tortilla. It wasn't bad. It was good. I inhaled it
Good and how you sharing I see you in the chat you little betrayer, but I still love you
Betrayal
Opera. Okay, I was thinking about going live real quick to talk more about the
Big Trollah Jen thing because I've heard more things that Big Trollah was saying and I'm like none of this is accurate
You know, and then I saw a post in regards to Skelly of the owls saying that he was gonna bust out some old clips
But but here's here's what people don't understand. Do you all realize that Jen is actually a lot younger than many of us?
She's only 33
But that's young. I mean, that's young. I mean, it's like and people think that she's older because she's you know
She's she she did live a very mature lifestyle very early, but she's only
30 and she's either 33 or 34. I think she's only 33
Yeah, well, that's what happened on good times today. I went on good times and she was in the good times chat and I was like
Hey as I check out and I know she's checked out your show
She was in the chat. She watches all my streams. I really you know
I'm gonna have to do a live just to give her some sort of guidance because you know about the 33 club
I'm sure you know that
33 I know that that's in Disneyland. There's like club 33, right?
Well, you know, you know the whole bad thing about it when it comes to people in the public eye when they're 30
That's it. You know things happen. I gotta make it through this year. Oh, we have another guest
This is squirrel's nest something you want to talk? I don't I don't know who that is. Oh, oh, it's it's 300 glow
Oh, okay
Hi, how are you doing tonight?
Look, he looks like Tom Cruise a little bit tonight.
I've been losing a lot of weight.
Look at the hair.
I like it.
Hey.
I lost a lot of weight already.
Two weeks.
Latino Tom Cruise.
Well, you know what this guy, I say,
he was in Money 420s, and he has a friend, and it looks like.
No, you can't.
I don't have a double chin no more.
You don't?
Oh my god, he looks good.
I have to admit, you do have like a spell.
You're looking spelled.
Yeah.
You know
300 glow he's glowing up
I've fasted for three weeks already you did what did you eat during that three weeks when you fasted? Oh yogurt
bananas
Black bananas and orange
Black bananas like they would they got
It was an actual black banana. I'm not like a black banana
But it took those bananas that like we sit on the microwave for a week
Yeah, okay, hey Eliza's asleep Charisma Hernandez is here
I know a lot of these people saw but I literally went to good times
I was like Jen I was like check out you know my show and check out Alex's show like she's been she's been having her back
He will be the goes but you don't have to tell look I have I have known I
Don't tell you the strange. I've never had a one-on-one conversation with her all after all these years
And it never needs to happen, but you don't have to ever inform her about anything about me and vice versa
But good times look see you just don't know good times yet good times
is always going to be a certain way.
He's in love with you, I can tell, because he goes,
you lied to me about Alexander, you said I drank mugwort.
No, it's not love, it's infatuation
and it's because he knows like, cared about him at one point.
Infatuation and what when?
I've just known him so many years and we got to know each other very very well, but
We don't have any communication
I wish him the best and whatever it is that he chooses to do or not do and that's the end of it
But don't trigger him
Okay
He hid me in his chat and he's like you were lying you're lying you're lying you cause you cause trouble
And you know you do man. No, I do but I wasn't trying it wasn't that much trouble
I just said he drank a tea and I'm okay if the tea's coming today in the mail. You were trolling him
Okay, you know what you were doing
It's me. Don't don't pretend like you weren't doing what you know, I won't I won't I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. No, and also there would be a little bit of jealousy on his end because he and I don't talk anymore
and he probably watches when I talk to you and
Sometimes people miss people but he made his decision and I'll tell you something really interesting when I really think about it
you know um
Just Jen strangely over the years has done me quite a few favors when it comes to
Um me having a very short attention span
When I was yeah, you don't know how to shut the fuck up. Hey
Yeah, really lose some weight and then come back before you tell me to shut the fuck up fat ass
Three well, you know, it's like you asked for it. I mean, that's what I mean. I don't know if people are so rude
I'm sorry about that. No, it's cool. But what I was saying is that
I do get to a point at times with people
when it's too frustrating.
And every single time,
just Jen has been there.
She was there to kind of take up the slack
and take over for me when it came to good times.
She did the same thing when it came to Tommy,
but she didn't follow through with Tommy.
She needs to make those jams.
I thought she was gonna make those jams for him.
How many months has it been?
Are they selling cocaine in the mail? I don't know what there's
He needs to probably give Tommy a call tonight because if she's gonna have to go to battle when it comes to Big Troll
There's really only one person in these communities who has consistently called out her
Victroleth bullshit, and you know who it is? Tommy. And the reason for that is because
no one knows addicts
like Tommy does, because he's the ultimate addict.
You cannot fool him if you're an addict you cannot trick him you cannot lie to him
He knows every single red flag in existence
He's always called out controller, which is why controller has always been mean to him
She's actually been colorist when it comes to him because she's like oh, it's a ginger. Yeah
Well, guess what just Jin's mama is a ginger, too. You don't always see the gingers
That's who she needs to talk to yeah, that is him
Right and you have to watch out for the gingers because like I think good times was saying today about Joe Shipley
He was like oh Joe he gets all hyper. He must be on like you know meth or speed. I'm like no
He's a ginger. They just are naturally different. They are different. Yeah wired like in a higher with the red hair
It's a fire. It's like a fire. They're on fire a lot
It's their national ginger that well, they they are a different kind of white person. I've always said that
They're my favorite white people really
They are because they are they are they're interesting. They're smart. They're smart as they can be smart as a whip
But at the same time then they have their temper. They have a temper and then and then the mischievous
Sensitive
Yeah
Doesn't help that it's like, you know their teeth because their hair is kind of orange and they have like orange body hair and stuff
Yeah, but it's like a pear face devil. I know well, I've been caught. There's the white devil. There's the orange devil
I don't know which is like
I will never in my life ever ever deal with another ginger again, but not in a certain capacity, but
Right they are a certain way
Most most of the most of the most of the white people I've gone along with best throughout my life have been
Ginger's not always right quite often and gingers and blacks do you have a certain thing in common?
The colorism my best friend like one of my best friends through high school and then after high school
She would come over we drink and watch TV and stuff. She was like
She's very short. She was like five foot one or something like that, but it was Megan
And she was she was adopted into a Jewish family like her her parents her birth parents with the Beverly Hills to give birth
So like we want a rich family to buy or to you know to adopt
A lot of Jewish people do adopt the gingers. It's interesting. Yeah
People are ginger actually, right
My dad like you know, I don't know like the story is not entirely clear why his first child was adopted
I just heard it
He's like was off was given the opportunity that he adopted a redhead boy like he says his first child that
That and he's like my older brother. He's he's the one that's I'm very into like Christianity and and more religious
I'm married to like a South African
Indian woman too. And so it's like we have a lot of like multiracial interesting things going on
But yeah, he was a bad, I mean, he was like always like getting into trouble.
He like, when he was younger, he got stuck to the pool drain.
And I always heard the story like, oh, you got sick of the pool drain and got off of it.
But there's a picture of him with the on a stomach.
He has a big red ring of the pool drain.
You told me about that.
Yes, they did.
I remember useful.
And that was such a strange thing.
But strange things happen to gingers. There's a lot of I did remember when I did the whole study on the ginger
Yeah
Right and it's like they shouldn't even biologically it's like dirt anomaly. They shouldn't exist
But I like what one interesting thing is like they have these albino albino. Oh, there's Christine in the chat
Oh, it looks she's screaming at you Alex. She's saying
drifter
Alexander watch let me read it Alexandra watch beat beat clip psyche lie to you
I've never said summer was a grifter or not to donate. Did you lie psyche? I didn't lie
I didn't like that. That's what I heard coming out of her mouth on Sam Man's clip
I think that was the BB clip but she said summer was doing a grift and she's saying and she and she said the same
Things about me too, but maybe I'll admit that sometimes I get things wrong or not
But yeah, I think William thinks Christine's an extra threshold.
I would agree with that.
Reminds me of like, you know, what Earth Girls are easy or something like that.
Wait, now Christine is an eating?
No, she's not.
Yeah, I think she is.
Well, why?
Does she have special powers?
She might.
I think she might.
She has special powers for insulting innocent gay white men.
I'm just kidding.
No, it's like, no, she's gonna dig in my ass.
She says, I dig in my ass.
My nails are back as I dig in my ass.
I mean, my nails are in my ass.
Sometimes we miss to remember things.
I miss to remember things all the time.
My nails are good.
Christine, I've always liked you, Christine.
It's like you will actually tell that to you
because I think he gets a little upset with me sometimes.
And I do.
I do.
And I mention that I like you.
I think that she's like, yeah.
I like you at the end of the day, too.
At the end of the day, I don't hate Christine.
At the end of the day,
i have good memories about her and she was there for me when i was going through my whole
channel going down and she has she has a good grandmotherly energy but the way she turned on
me and but she's not what's up call it give me a she's not that much older than really and i think
she has like 10 grandkids i mean i how many grandkids good for her she managed to reproduce
better than me i'm trying to do it i'm like an emergency state
Christine! I'm hearing that you're a witch. Could you cast the spell of fertility and drawing in the right man for me to procreate as soon as possible?
Because I only have a few words left, okay? Help me, Christine! Cast the spell!
It does on eyes and mouth.
I would never say that about some okay. Maybe if I got it wrong. I got it wrong and I have all right
So we got it cleared up. Nobody be mad because I like Chris
No, Christine you are you it's like you know that you are one of my best friends
Don't even think otherwise, but I do like things about Christine. I just do
I just you I mean I even like even somebody I can say I don't like I can find some things about them
I like I mean and so I understand like there are
Yeah, there you go and Christine's gonna help me with her with her craft
Yeah
I would love Christine to come up and say hi to you because I've never I never say even if she insults me
It's fine
Because I'd love to I'd love to have you guys say hi because Christine like you know even when Alice was mad at me at a
certain point she was
Kind of zeroed in on you a little bit like and how like, you know
You are interesting person and you have likable qualities. And so I mean, I don't even want to come up and say hi or whatever
I'm not gonna be tell her what to do. I'm asking if she wants to I'm not yeah, but if she wants to come on up
You know, it's like, but I'm not gonna like insult her or be mean to her or treat her like she's treated me
I'm willing to put by God's be bike on and maybe you can maybe you can be like a piece of broker in a certain way
You're like the UN
Yeah, you give you an energy you have this you who am I gonna be am I gonna be Meghan Markle now?
You're you're hotter than Meghan Markle. I mean come on. No, I'm not. She's beautiful. I am not hotter than Meghan Markle
You're definitely how you have princess energy or Queen energy actually
I do have Queen energy, but I am not gonna take Meghan Markle's
Extreme Meghan Markle if you've ever seen her in person though when she's on camera
I've seen her in person. The camera doesn't do her justice. She is absolutely
And look who she's with she's with the ginger, right?
You're right. I that's in you across my mind. It's my mind, but it didn't cross my mind like like thinking about it
But well because when you're ginger, that's as far on the spec on the spectrum of ethnicity
Really when you think about it as you can go into like you can't like what's beyond ginger?
nothing no
Genetic diversity
And you know, maybe that's why those Pleiadians are coming here. Maybe maybe they need some.
So I got to watch out because I'm telling you those Pleiadian men, they live a long time.
And to them, I'm going to seem like I'm young. They're going to be coming after me. So I got to get ready.
I have to get one of my own on Etsy. They have these readers. They're like, oh, we'll tell you your alien background
And so I bought one of these readings or whatever and then she sent a picture without even seeing the picture of me or anything
She said a picture looks very much like me. I was more blonde and it was like you're Pleiadian
I had like like a kind of you probably are you I would say I think that the guy was married to might have been at least
Apart because he looks like the renderings that they make of them. I'm not sure. I'm arturian
I don't know if you know
What I know about our curious is it is like the like the higher octave of the brain is
If there's any alien is our curry and everything about that resonates with how I feel
They're teachers, they're very wise, they're builders.
They probably are kind of the architect energy.
And I know Capricorn's have a heavy architect energy,
so I do think you have Mark Turian in you too.
I mean, it's like, he's your builder.
I mean, it's like, you can build things.
That's what I do.
Yeah, I can't help it.
And my dad was an engineer.
Yeah.
I think he definitely had that.
spiritual energy coming through him.
That's where I think it really came from.
I don't know if you know this, but when I was,
like my last official job I had
where I was assistant to a CEO for a couple of years,
but we were, it was actually,
we were one of NASA's like outsourcers
and NASA would hire us to do the Hubble telescope
inspections of the parts in Asia and stuff.
And so we would hire engineers to go to China and stuff
to examine like the little lenses and stuff
for the Hubble telescope.
And so there's a lot of weird synchronicities about that.
Like I actually say, I work for NASA in some kind of respect
because we would do the outsourcing for them
and hire people for them.
I love engineers.
Engineers have a quirky mind.
They have a little bit of the autistic kind of thing going on
where they're like kind of like...
You know a little bit like a guy with a sandwich
Like the AI the AI is modeled
Unfortunately, but also fortunately it's gonna take the AI a long time to really figure out human emotion
sarcasm quirks, but they really programs the AI I mean the person who I have
Intentatively picked out to be
My paternal contributor. He's on the spectrum. I don't have I know I'm on the spectrum to an extent
But he does do the programming for the AI and I don't think it's really a
Because I think it's a sort of evolution. I think that as humans we're starting to split into different species
I'm really starting to think that.
And I think that people that are so against AI,
they're suspicious to me as like almost like competitors
or like they're like, I don't know, like a whole AI
or something like that.
It's been already predicted
that there's gonna be split offs with their humanity.
So you're gonna go more along the lines
of probably wherever I go, which is great
because we're best friends.
So you better come with me, I won't be by myself.
Yes, I mean it's like, like, AI really is like,
I mean, if we can work with it in the right way,
it is like-
May I use my powers very quickly?
Well, no, I can't, because this person's a moderator.
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm just gonna use my-
What do you want to add?
I don't want, well, I just don't want them
to pick on Christine.
Not right now.
I just feel-
You shouldn't be pecked on I guess I guess
Chrismas can you just lay off Christine a little bit because your Christmas is a good mod and I know she might have
Yeah, and I don't I'm not countering charisma. I don't know who charisma is
But it's just something about Christine that resonates with me. I don't know exactly, but I just it's something about her
I just really like
Yeah
Well, I'll tell you what it is. I like that. She acknowledges her gifts. I like that. She tells it like it is
For her perspective as to how it is. I like that
She's bold
Right. I like that. You know, I guess that makes me very you're well your friend. Um, what's the pretty girls named prairie?
Prairie when I first met Prairie, you know what she said to me and I take as such a compliment because no one has said that to me for
Years because people don't recognize within me. I am a girl's girl. I'm a very girly girl deep down and
Prairie page did recognize that in me. I don't get to show it a lot
But that's what makes me really like Christine because Christine is a girl's girl. That's what it is, but and prairie page two is like
Really a gem in the community because she has like such a good heart even and she like, you know
I mean, it's like almost like me if I was like actually could like implement my good heart like she actually has
Yeah, she actually has like the oh, you know, you must be like hurting or like she just gets his
She's somebody who's
internal beauty is not as beautiful as her external. And she's incredibly beautiful externally,
but you can just see it within her. I saw it, especially within her when she had a friend
on with her one night and I was watching the stream. It's something about her environment,
the culture she comes from, who she is.
The energy also that she attracts she's a very good person. How would you like it?
If like you're in a sorority and she was like some kind of like member of the sorority
I mean, it's like I almost they think it like that where it's like she that's a girl
Right. It's like hey like hey girls. Let's have fun
But we're also like we're smart as hell and we can like to take over too, but it's like let's uh
You know, we can move we're we're hotties too and it's like I just love that kind of energy
She's a very she's a sugar sweet girl
Yeah, but she doesn't want anyone to know so yeah
Yeah, but that's it's you know a lot of people that I've
You know even briefly connected to through you have helped me learn a lot about yourself or myself rather
Yourself too. I'm sure but myself. I want to thank you for that
You you you have been a very bright light like a lighthouse for me
I've been going through, you know, I don't always admit it, but when you and I connected,
it was such a perfect time.
And I also want to thank Gotti, because if Gotti had not been on the panel when I initially
And I love that too because Gotti is like, you know, Gotti and I are very different personalities too
But it's like and he came here to troll me. He even admits it and it was like he was
Oh, really?
Well, you came here to troll me but he and I'm saying he fell in love with me
But I'm saying he we came to like a mutual respect like and that I'm in love with I'm in love with his voice
I'll admit I crush on I have fantasies about him. I do. It's wild. I think he's taken
I think his girlfriend has pink hair
I've noticed this. So I'm not after your man, whoever the girl is, but it's something about him
that's very comforting. It's his voice. I'm very sensitive to voices.
Marcy Fox, are you dating Gotti? I don't know if you know Marcy Fox. She has pink and blue hair.
Well, all his videos revolve around a girl with pink hair. So that's his girl.
Right. She's like, God, he's God, and then he does like these hour long songs and all of this God, he is God, like bad down to God.
I mean, it's like, it's ridiculous, but no, that's how they make love cerebral.
That's what I know. I don't go on is I looked at his channel, I saw what they were doing.
And I was like, whoa, this is a little too much for me. I feel like I'm looking at something I shouldn't be looking at.
I mean, he's starting his own cult following, you know, and it's like, I like that it's like, because everything is a cult
I think that's like the whole point like I never wanted to say I'm like this evil cult or I don't think
Cult cults all it means to me is culture and it's a culture that revolves around. I gave you that didn't I? Yeah. Yeah
Culture and it's like
It's like, you know, when we all live in a culture, we can live in our work culture, we can live in our, our internet culture, and all these, we're on, we're in a lot of cults, and it's like, and so we don't even know, because we, we haven't said that some kind of scary, forbidden thing, or mysterious, but all it is, all it is, is like who we are attracted to, our group, our, our soul tribe, that's our culture.
It is, and sometimes our tribes overlap, and we don't always like when they overlap, because I know I'm a brat about it.
God knows I am. But I'm a selfish friend. I am. When I feel like somebody is a part of my tribe, I am just like, whoosh!
You belong to me now. That's how I feel you know
I in this whole thing with Jen actually has helped me understand more the situation between you and beta
believe it or not because
it has
because I
Am I am I was thinking about this today because the whole situation with Jen has bothered me all day today. I
Am protective over that young woman
And I don't feel like I should be, but I just am because I saw her grow up.
I got to know her family, which is so odd because I've never spoken to her.
We've spoken through chat, but I've never verbally spoken to her.
I've never met her in person.
Her brother chased me down on Fremont Street.
a few years back when I was in the Las Vegas area.
It was her mother who initially contacted me.
There's someone else, and I'm not sure it's a male who contacted me.
It's got to be her father, I would think.
But I've never spoken to her and I don't want to because I don't think that it's necessary
But I am protective of her because I just see her as a young girl
Growing up if she's and people just do forget how young she is and that bothers me
You know, she was thrust into a situation
don't know exactly why but to where she had to grow up fast but she's a mom now
and it kills me that there's these two women who I also got to know Tricia and
Carissa who are doing this shit to her when they were once they they should be
able to relate to her more than I ever could
So why would you want to hurt your past self? Why? I don't like that. It bothers me. It hurts me
right
Like I wouldn't have thought that it would hurt me like this it hurts me
It makes me want to just pound those women to the ground really
And I won't but that's what it makes me feel because I think to myself. I'm like you got this young girl
try
just to try and
You can't help her
Yeah, I mean it's like she I think you should talk to each other because no
and the reason I don't know because
I am turning a certain page in my life.
I just want her to know that I have always tried.
And that's it, OK?
If I wish I could go back in time
and not answer her mom's email, I
wish I could go back in time and not
have ever entered these communities.
I do, because it's been problematic for me.
That people do get it when it comes to her and she's done a good job. And that's it. She's done a good job
And sometimes that's what it's about just letting somebody know that they've done a good job. I think about um,
Sorry, I know
No, I don't know her is they oh, yeah
I will I even know almost exactly when her child was conceived because I got to know her child's father
Did you understand I know her entire story? It's crazy. I don't like knowing that young girl story
It's too much for me
It's been too much
Yeah, I mean, it's like she said Alex like me it at worst or whatever, but it's like no
Yeah, I never should have been involved. I know that there's a reason so I know there's a reason as to why
But I'm not I had to I had to go to such an extent to tell her mom to tell her brother
Hey, just let me be
Because they love her
And I just and I don't know why you know
If you hear this Jen, I want you to really listen to me
You're online friends. Good times
You can trust Tommy
I know it's weird I'm saying this to you, but you can, you can't trust what he says about me, but you can trust him when it comes to him doing right by you, when it comes to what he knows, when it comes to a battle that you might have to fight.
That will be your best ally. You can trust like he'll guide you right, but you got to stop when it comes to certain things because you're putting yourself in danger.
And you know that the danger is not just IRL. You know what the danger is which I will not speak on here
but pretty well as far as I can see like she's like
Classing herself up a little bit. She's doing her hair doing her makeup like
She always has presented extremely well that was part of the reason why she
certain things that she's achieved. She has always been beautiful, she has always known how to fix herself up, she's always known how to speak. She always has known, she just, I think maybe the reason that her mom did contact me all those years ago was that there's some things within me that are similar to her daughter, you know, and maybe she saw it.
But Jim just needs to be very discriminatory when it comes to who she lets in her life.
If she needs to also listen to her husband now.
Not just her mom, not just her brother, not just her father, but her husband.
Yeah.
Hold on.
Let's take one.
There you go.
Sorry, Matt.
We're kicking out both of us right now.
Okay.
Give me my last drink.
Thank you
Good, okay. Thank you good night
Sorry
Any one more drink
And having my little pinot noir tonight. That's my drink of the evening pinot noir
Oh, my favorite is Cabernet Sauvignon, like that was like our drink is with my uh,
I write Cabernet too and like if there's no Pinot Noir, I will have Cabernet.
I prefer the Pinot Noir because it has a little bit of a tartness to it normally.
And um, this particular one, I'm drinking one called Angeline.
Which is a I'd like that name and I if I were to have a daughter
I would name her Angelina. I would at least consider it because it's such a nice name and Richard Martin John Boy
Yeah, Angelina Jolie, but but Richard Marks made this beautiful song called a called Angelina
I always loved that song
so
And I've always loved Richard Marks. That's one of my favorite artists
And you know angels are like highly associated with Saturn because they got the EL and that's like very associated with Saturn and the Saturn rules like the
Capricorn so we have like a high connection to these angels. I believe like a capricorn. We do
Yeah
We do.
January birthdays, December birthdays,
I think they were in the threshold.
And also like Janus, like January.
And Janus was like the Roman,
even like, I guess Ganesha or the Roman,
the god of the beginning of Rome.
And that's why they had this gate of Janus,
which is an archway, right?
And that was like the archway into Rome.
And we have these archways everywhere.
And so it's very bad.
And about the builders the architects fathers, I mean it's like that all those
I think we're about to learn a lot about what we're like. I think that what we I think that what we
Think of as angels
May not have been angels, but I think that what we don't think of as angels are real
Right. Oh
Miss Sharon sometimes I gotta I gotta stop being mean to Sharon because I miss her
Well, I know I'm not Sharon and you're sad Sharon was you're like the only one
The reason I got mad at Sharon was because she was moderating for other people and all this kind of stuff
And I got locked into the drama
But Sharon should not be surprised if she finds herself as a moderator again in my chat
Okay.
Oh, that's sweet.
Because I've got to have the wrong-
I've got to have the wrong channels.
Uh-oh. Well, I guess it's now time for Alexander to take over.
He's back. He's back.
Alright, let's park him over here.
Lunar, you come over here and say hi to Alex.
This is my beautiful, I love beautiful black cats.
Yeah, what up kitty? What up sister?
I haven't seen him. I haven't seen him.
Meow, meow, meow.
Yeah, and Mola comes over.
Lola, Lola, she, Lola sees Linor getting attention.
They're like little like, you know,
cause Lola got pregnant,
but Linor was fixed before she ever got pregnant.
And so like, Linor hated Lola,
but then once Lola got pregnant,
Linor got an interest in her.
Just, what's going on?
Like, why are you getting fat?
Why are you like sleeping under the TV all the time?
And then when Lola had the babies,
Lenore was like really like I was afraid Lenore would be like attacking the babies or attacking
But she became so respectful to her and like was like wow and like Lenore kind of like an auntie and you know
She and she still likes the babies like they come over once in a while
If you're a solid good female
Even if you're not if you don't have children or you're not able to you're always going to look after other women's children
You just do it. Yeah, and it's weird because sometimes what like as a woman who as of this moment even though I'm gonna try next year
child-free by choice
Sometimes you know when you're a woman
Who doesn't have the children and you look at other women with children, especially if those women are mean to you you get mad
and you're like
Don't you see
What I lack
and how it hurts, why are you hurting me more?
But I don't think that the women with the children
to where it was oh so like a default.
They understand no because they're still in that mindset of like the being petty with people and stuff like that and not understanding like
They're getting some respect or they're getting some like love and prop and that their kids are loved
And it's like people do care about the well-being of children like in a big way, especially women, right? And it's like so
So it's like it. There's like a respect there to them and it's like a nation
recognition recognize it and
Maybe a little bit nicer because it's like we're not all in
That's why God is known and not just the Christian God other
deities or
The systems of belief to their higher powers
Women if you have children and you're picking on women who don't you better be careful because
What you think you have will be taken
Happened I mean the most famous story I would say in the Bible would be when
God sent the angel to Egypt to get rid of the firstborns
Could you imagine dealing with that? Oh my god, I mean
Right and they had like the blood of the lamb they put the like lamb blood over there
They're their doorway to show which houses had male children and what which didn't and they got away by doing that
And that's what we're in these communities
I said this for years and I and I have had other actually, you know who it was who acknowledged
What I was saying about this and that's why I can't believe that big troll is doing this to Jen
It was Victrola saying you know Alex is right about the mothers of sons coming after the mothers of daughters
I've started realizing that within the ETC thing and you know what else because I'm gonna recap those ETC recent streams
When they're just hanging out with cousin Dutchie mr. Ninja travels
Because they're out of balance. They only got one girl that they're running around with heavies and she digs a house
girl she has to get she's twice the size she was when she first arrived at HS3 or HS2
whatever that was comfortable is I think her and Zay are eating pretty well you know it's like I
don't know they are they're eating everything the refrigerator is empty around them but you know
what I mean it's like uh yeah and Pam's also has like a very masculine energy to her she's
Ask the energy to and it's like maybe zealous chicken cakes. So does amber all the women that he's are they really even spiritually women?
That's the question
might not be
Right, I mean I feel that I mean it's like some of them I do have like I mean I say I think you know
I do go with the thing about like, you know
We're born of a male and a female and so we have both these sides and maybe an androgynous person is kind of like
We're getting more and more androgynous as we go into because we're all these males
Yeah, our males and females born from males and females right and so it's like and it is very androgynous now
I don't know if you saw the thing I played the other night. It was about kind of like
started with the Mona Lisa and the Mona Lisa is probably a male. It was probably like Leonardo
da Vinci's lover and then a lot of people have speculated that. Yes. Yeah. Also,
since people say it was like the first photograph, there's a big thing where Da Vinci set up this
big thing in his room with like a sheets and like, and like a lecture magnet and there's some kind
of photo first photo. I was going to say the shroud of her and that was the first photo. Yeah.
I mean it became a photo because the energy from what Jesus was connected to was so strong
That it burned that shroud. That's how that shit happened. That was x-ray type energy that created that
That tell you about what Jesus really was
Right, did you ever notice on the shroud that there are owls on the shroud just like yes
Yeah, well you you need to do a stream
I hope at some point skelly and you do a stream together because I met him
I had a wonderful hike with him. I fell in love with him a little bit
He gave it, you know at Q45 picks on me about this, but I don't get a shit and I'm not after him
But I did crush on him a little bit. Good thing 24 eyes was there. That was the buffer
Skelly is very special. I wouldn't say I fell in love with him
but he I fall in love with very unusual energies as you know and
He
gave me such a beautiful hike and a beautiful trip.
He went above and beyond to try,
so many things went wrong on that trip, but he tried.
And that's why despite certain things, I just, I'm glad.
He's back, and I hope that he keeps covering these streamers
I hope that he does delve into the lore that he knows when it comes to certain things and he really is
The reason Tommy don't like him is because Skelly is a solid alpha
I have not come across many especially as young as he's young too. I don't even know these 30
When I think about he's very young very mature for his age when he's young
And he has that alpha energy like a wolf pack leader.
It's crazy, but kind.
And Trisha should be ashamed of herself
for going against him,
especially after everything that he did for her.
He's a real community leader.
Real, not just online, in person.
All those women who have been mean to him
should be ashamed of themselves.
Yeah, happy Father's Day Scali
Yeah, I mean
It looks like he's has a good setup. It seems like he's like a good streamer like has a good good, you know
very smart very
Down home if you know what I mean when I say that uh-huh
He's a down home kind of guy and he good. He comes from good parents
Yeah
I mean, yeah, I mean, it's like I just see like, you know, like people turning against people and I don't know
I don't know all the lore and all like the backgrounds of everybody
I don't know if you've heard the latest clip that beat beat posted about Big Trollah
It I didn't I didn't hear everything that she said but in that clip that was just posted. She says oh
I already knew Jen was gonna turn on me. I feel like just shaking that girl just shaking her
Because Jen was not gonna turn on her. I hate when people say turn on turn. No, no, no, no, no
Yeah, we turned on Jen before Jen could defend herself
And what it came down to was that both Victrola and Trisha, I think thought that they had it in the bag
and they thought that certain people, including myself,
weren't gonna say something.
I will always say something if I'm capable of doing so
when it comes to that young girl, Jen,
because I just know what she has gone through
versus what she hasn't, where she's lied
versus where she's told the truth,
and a few other things too.
So if you're gonna talk about somebody,
Yeah
That's me being angry for today
Alice have you seen my my latest I have a new intro for the show and it's like I have I have
Criticisms of it, but I do like it. He was playhouse one. He's on Peewee's play
It's no the wine first like he's nightmares the intro
Everywhere you look everywhere you go. It's
Do you want me to redo it for you?
Yeah, you can redo it. Yeah, I mean, yeah, I mean absolutely, but I mean I kind of do
Like it, but it's not it's not what it should be for you and not in my opinion because
And I'm not criticizing what you but it's it's just that I'm an asshole. It's okay
Okay, yeah, and I want your and I want your thing to have a certain
Vibe, and I just know what it's missing. Hey real quick, and then I want you to see what you would do to it
All right. Well, do you mind if I interrupt as you're playing it?
Just yeah, here we go. So this is the intro we're gonna be working on this is
Take take take the children out of it. Oh, yeah, okay. Yeah, I mean they're just like it is like the 80s and stuff like that
So the other day they manifest those but they're not real
Well, I know they're not real people but just because you already deal with what you deal with why why
They're all gonna be like 18
Well, yeah, make them teenagers not not
Okay, thank you
All right, I'm going to tell you what I like about it.
What I like about it is that the sound reminds me
of that song, Rock the Cradle of Love.
Remember that song?
Yeah.
That's what it is.
Same pattern and also similar.
Who's saying that song?
Was it Billy Idol?
Yeah, I think it was Billy Idol.
I think you're right, yeah.
OK.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're doing me to it.
If you have young teens one thing take the reason I say take the kids out of it because you're really not a family friendly show
Let's let's keep it real and you're right. The best idol is cradle of love
Yeah, and it's gonna remind people of that song rock the cradle of love
So it's they're gonna be like, ooh, this is too much. Okay, but let's keep going
Nobody's there when it rains
The street
Something follows every beat
The neighbor's smile with glowing
Every friendly waves a disguise
Every way you look
But nobody
Morns and mothers gone
H.S. rewinds itself again
There's a go
We don't
I'm gonna tell you right now. I really love everything about it with the exception of the minute things that I criticize
Okay, it's beautiful. I mean, it's I I mean as we get closer to Halloween, it's gonna be so
perfect
But it's you and it's the macabre is the drama is the nostalgia of the 80s
It's it's it's us when we were younger. It's great
The only thing that you're gonna have to be conscientious of is
Yeah, I'm not you're not family friendly and neither am I what we can't be
We're for grown-ups. I have a treat for you something. I've been working on. It's not near completion. I
Just rendered it while we were
Talking it's it does feature
You are you ready? Yeah, I'm ready. All right, let me upload it
But that but what I was thinking of my that video was like a run-of-the-pewies playhouse the introduction to that
Yes, but you don't want to be you don't want when you know what happened to yeah, and nothing good happens
That's why you don't want to emulate that. No, I understand
Understand your attraction to it, but no, yeah, that was a kid. I was a kid when that was for kids
I mean, yeah when it was
Seen for it, but we as adults we know what happened. I got you. I got you. Exactly. So
You know, I know that you love the controversy as I do but being that I'm two years older than you are
In my old
Years as as your as your senior
I'm just telling you make it easy on yourself. Yeah. Well, why not?
It's a green advice
All right, let me let me let me give you something hold on
Rendered properly it's it's it's in the works. It's in progress. Okay. Good
It makes it more like I'm more realistic that it's backstage and it is. Oh, you're working on it already. Okay. Here we go
Nothing on TV
So I have a model and there they were
Been watching the bad moms
Bad moms from the panel
Can we watch it again? Can we watch it again?
It was because yeah, this is this is this is to me
You are you are this guy you're a model and your designer
And this is your arena. You are fashion
Thanks, so I'm I'm will do not well. Maybe you don't want to be fast
I have a fashion version degree by my my look closely at that jacket. What do you see on that jacket?
The YouTube YouTube screens or something. Yes. Yeah, that's because you're the YouTube designer
I love it. I love it. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. And you're on the runway. Are you a designer? Are you the model? We don't know.
My face is pretty good. Look at that. There you go. That is me. Well, that is your, yeah. I worked up. I'm working on it. This is just a little preview of what I'm working on, ultimately. Okay.
But I felt you should see. Friday night again.
Nothing on TV
So I open YouTube
Yeah, the bat mom's are probably murder me but yeah
I love that, I love that.
I'm a bad mom, this is a live streaming.
Hey, I'm just glad I'm not a mom.
I wouldn't want to be a mom on a live stream.
I mean, it's like, I mean, it'd be a little bit too.
I mean, I barely like having cats
that have been on a live stream.
I think my kids, I don't think I can imagine a kid.
Look at the mom.
Well, maybe we could turn all the bad moms
into good moms if we push hard enough, you know?
Because they want to be good.
They just don't, I don't think they know how.
Yeah, it's in love, like totally out of love.
I mean, it's like, you know, it's like, hey, correct yourself.
Kind of like, you know, hint, hint, like, you know.
In a loving way not and I like oh, you know if you just do it in a good way
And I and it's like and I hope they should listen to you
I mean everything I mean it's really you have your really brilliant what you're very wise
And and you've been through things and it's like they'd be wise to take your advice about things because you have that
Um, the outsider kind of perspective but being on the inside at the same time
I don't know how to describe it right, but it's like you just I
The other night we were talking and you know, we were both drinking and whatnot
I was you know, you were saying some incredibly
Complementary things to me and I didn't want to take it because sometimes I don't want to acknowledge
Who I am, but you're right. You were right the other night
I do have a lot of nurturing energy, but I don't know what to do with it because
I don't really have anywhere that is like the designated output right right now
I mean it's like women are nurturers and even for like like men
It's like men are like kind of like these permanent babies women from the early age
are no crystal land reference here, but with the dolls.
Women are very like, they love to take care of dolls,
like they're real human beings and stuff like that.
Well, animals too.
I mean, I might end up having to just have
a whole bunch of animals.
And if I do, I'm just going to buy a farm or a ranch.
And you know what I'm going to raise?
Goats.
Yes
Black woman raising a shitload of goats if I don't achieve my goal next year
And that is what I will be doing and I'm gonna train my goats to be attacked goats
And that way anyone who tries to fuck with me I'll be like hey come on out to my property. Let's see what happens, huh?
And it's gonna be me and my little goats
If that's what it comes down to and that will just be my pathetic life and the goats on the camp goes our Capricorns and ghosts also
What do they do? I'm gonna try to breed unicorns
I'm gonna try to breathe them down one horn instead of two and then I can finally
into my life raising the last unicorns,
because that is my favorite movie.
I like that idea, and it's like,
the milk comes out in rainbow colors.
You know, you can like, you know.
No, I'm not gonna let people have their milk or anything.
I'm not gonna let people have their babies yourself.
No, not even for me, it's for their offspring.
I'm not gonna let people mess with my goats,
if I have to.
They can live there and be free as free as they can be on my property and be happy and
they can love me and then when I drop dead, they can maybe I can train them to go for
help.
You know, they can train them to help me and be like, oh, our owner's dead.
We better do something.
I know you might have seen this. I mean, I think I showed this to you, but you know
I what I do want to show you what happens when you mix a spider with a goat
I mean, it's like oh, I've already seen that. Yeah
This is one minute. This is one minute. All right
It's to see what happens when you mix a spider with a goat because magic happens actually
This is actually true. This is true. This is right here, and I would not have to cut my grass
if I had goats
I mean, they would eat the grass, the goats are very,
it's like a whole recycling center in an animal.
Oh, they would probably love me.
They would be happy.
Check this out.
Scientists created goats that produce spider silk.
Yes, inside their milk.
Instead of farming spiders, which is almost impossible,
researchers took a spider gene
and inserted it into a goat's DNA.
Now, when the goat produces milk, it also produces silk proteins.
Those proteins are extracted and spun into fibers stronger than steel, lighter than aluminum,
and incredibly flexible.
This material is known as bio steel, and it could be used for surgical sutures, bulletproof materials, even aerospace technology, but here's the question, should we be engineering animals like this, or is this where science goes too far?
It is an interesting question.
Is it going too far?
No, if they can create an aluminum silk jacket that is bulletproof.
I mean, how many of these sell?
This will be the next fashion thing, right?
I mean, it's like these beautiful silk outfits that are bulletproof.
I mean, that's going to be the next generation I think it will.
You know it's like these these fabrics that are that are not even like possible and naturally
I mean once we figure out how to mix goat DNA and spider DNA. Yeah, we can make this but I mean
That's pretty intense though, right? It's like it's just I mean it's interesting. Well, I mean think about the movie spider-man
I mean, I've always thought that the Marvel Comics writers are people who are
Futurists people ahead of their time able to see things that
We don't necessarily know are coming spider-man really think about what spider-man was about think about the mechanics and the
science
Right well, you know how he became spider-man, right?
Was it in a lab experiment gone awry?
Well, he got bitten by a radioactive spider. Okay. Yeah
Yeah
Yeah. I mean, that'll do it. That'll do it. I mean, it's like, okay. So I would I we used to spend a lot of time in Palm Springs
And we had these black widows in Palm Springs. You just want me
But they would be in the pool drains. We'd see these
And then one time before we left Palm Springs for like, you know, a few months
We found this egg sack behind the tv. So there'd be 500 black widows in the room
Like next thing you came in if you didn't get that egg sack out. I mean, it's a date, but there is there's some pretty crazy
I mean this spider can like paralyze a human being you know or kill human beings
I mean it's like so and they have very they have an hourglass on their butts of an hour a red hourglass
And it's just very yeah, right. I mean so the nature is so amazing
I don't know if you've seen the the birds of paradise. Have you ever heard of the birds of paradise?
Yes, yes, okay, so there's birds of paradise and these are birds in South America and
There's like they're the most beautiful birds. Oh, well, it's also it's also a flower
It's also a type of plant right
And it looked like the birds of flower birds
Okay, you this real quick this look at this bird right here. Look and this is amazing
I think you will be you'll be shocked. We can check this out. Check this out. I think you'll love this
So this is a bird of paradise. Well, I do like birds. Yeah, I love this one. You'll love this. I promise
Okay, so here it is. Check this out here. We got it. Okay. You got it on the screen
Here we go. Oh, okay. Yeah, here we go right here
This isn't all the bird of paradise. Okay. Look at this bird
the character of the forest changes as you descend becoming ever darker and damper favoring different kinds of animals and plants
Less than 2% of the sunlight reaches the floor, but even here, there is extraordinary variety.
In the great island of New Guinea, there are 42 different species of birds of paradise, each more bizarre than the last.
And birds have an extensive vocabulary. I've had birds that pet many times.
Yeah
It was a boy actually
It was such a pretty bird I always called it a girl I had this dirt named peaches
My dog did but I learned Peaches language basically like it and I've come across other love birds in my life
And I know how to do the vocalizations and the birds that they look at you crazy because they're like, how do you know what we're saying?
How do you know how to talk to us?
Yeah, um, but they have very distinct ways that they communicate
Like we had an African gray parrot my mom actually raised lovebirds like where we had that her birds gave
My only mistake was that nobody told me that they should be in pairs
The worst thing that I ever did to peaches was not get peaches a mate
That's why when I have parakeets later. I got the parakeet quarry a mate because
That they need to have they need that they cannot be by themselves. They're too lonely and they get so sad
Yeah, and often as they do I think but yeah, I think my mom ahead like you know
My mom would hand feed these birds like once they're born you have to yeah
You get them a little feeder you get it or you get a little syringe full of like, you know this high protein bird food
You put it like
And they like fruit too, they when they're bigger they like to eat fruit
Mango they love mangoes and they like
peaches and pears that mine like peach a lot. So I that's why he was named peaches
My grandma never named Dickey bird. She always had a canary named Dickey. They didn't have a canary named Dickey
She had another canary named Dickey, and then the American named Dickey got very very
His feathers got all messed up and stuff
But she didn't have an answering machine that she recorded where when I was like little and then I call in
and she wouldn't answer the phone and that she had the birds singing in the background so beautifully and it's like and so
I mean
Because they do learn how to talk
It was singing beautiful song
Melody and stuff like that like but I had I had on parakeets. I had um
I had like the larger parakeets and I had, I've had a conures, I had a conure named Lucy, we didn't
interrupt her Lucifer because she was so mean and stuff, but yeah, and she was a redhead,
and she was, she had like a little redhead, and we had this wild actually in the area right here,
they're called cherry-headed conures, and I guess they, they broke out of like a pet store truck
in the like the 1920s. They probably did, they escaped. Yeah, they escaped, and they're all over
the area, and it's like, and I also do certain mantras, and there's a certain goddess,
that has always flocked by these birds. But when I do this goddess's mantra, the birds appear.
I mean, that's why I know God, I think the mantras work is because it would be impossible.
The birds are very, they somehow know what people are safe. When I was living in LA, I had a
It was a pigeon, which you would call a dove, but I found it one day when I was coming home from work
There's a lot of trained white pigeons that they released for weddings in Los Angeles
Sometimes they get lost and I found this one it for some reason it was sitting right outside my balcony
But I had a screen on my balcony and I couldn't get to it
I was dating the guy at the time and he was bringing me back from somewhere
I was and I saw the bird because I'd seen it twice before and I was like
There's that bird again, and he was like you want me to go and get it for you
And I'm like if you want to if it'll if it won't fly away, but he liked animals too
So he was able to grab this bird. I called it Philip
And I had that bird the entire time I was in Los Angeles for a couple years, and when
I moved, I did let it go.
And it was fine. I hopefully I mean these animals need to be out like they're like outdoor animals
Like I'm old and once you raise them from the baby
One was used to people. I think it was a wedding
Dove that got lost
But it liked being where but I couldn't keep it and when I had to move I had to move
And I didn't have anywhere to take it to so I just opened I cut
the screen where I lived and I was like, well, if it's meant to fly away, it will.
And it did, and it never came back because I did it a few days before I moved
to see if it would come back because if it came back, I would have taken it with me.
But I want to show you I have this this video I sent on my friend
I think I'm gonna send this Karen, but there's this cat named Cheeto and a squirrel named nuts
okay, and
Squirrel or Cheeto and nuts fall in love if you can just take this out real quick. This is like
So cute like take this out. So this is Cheeto and nuts. Let me see if it's on the screen. I think you'll love this
Okay
not closely watch them if not you see a squirrel cat but I'm ready to take the
cat if anything happens but Cheeto started to lick his fur like he was one
of his siblings and nuts had this look on his face like what are you doing buddy
They didn't care if one was a squirrel and one was a cat.
They don't care when they're low.
Why is that curious thing ever?
Nuts would play with him and snuggle with him.
At that moment I thought,
Okay, is this relationship going to be something that lives on forever?
Well, yeah
But about two months ago my wife and I went to go meet Cheeto
When I instantly fell in love
We already had a dog at home Ruger. He's like an old man
So I was worried about how Cheeto would react because he was only nine weeks old at the time
Ruger
Cheeto was actually the one who walked up and I'm like oh my gosh he's going
right up to him but Ruger just kind of ignored him so we put Ruger away in his
bedroom and Cheeto kind of hangs out with us until one night I couldn't find
Cheeto anywhere.
He's in here with Ruger, sleeping on them.
He's not enjoying this.
But he's...
And from that moment on, I'd see them slowly getting comfortable with one another,
but then all of a sudden, nuts came into our life.
We were taking Ruger on a walk.
I looked down on the ground and there was this little tiny squirrel and it was shaking.
I said, hey, little guy, come here.
Well, a squirrel just walked into my hand.
I felt like Nuts chose me to be his new dad.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's a squirrel in my pocket.
I actually went back the next day
to see if I could see any squirrels.
No, he wanted to go in.
I went online and I researched how can I rehabilitate
and help raise this squirrel.
He's so hungry.
Chido was honestly the first one to accept nuts.
At night Chido would just sit by nuts his house and just stare and like touch it with
his feet like he wanted to play and then chase each other a little bit and I think it was
very important at the time of their life where they bonded but for now I think nuts place
So I made his little house put it in the tree and I say okay, here you go buddy. This is your new home
And he just jumped in it and I was just like okay. I think he likes it
Where are you nuts?
Nuts you're going high buddy. It was bittersweet honestly
But then when it was time for nuts to go Cheeto and Ruger they had already connected
Now Cheeto he's a copycat
If Ruger lays down in his bed, what happens?
Cheeto comes and lays right next to him.
Yeah.
And they're just kind of inseparable.
And you know, people in a strange way are like that.
So everything worked out really perfectly.
There you go, yeah.
I mean, I'm sorry.
Yeah.
People in a strange way.
are similar to, you know, different types of the animals.
Cause when animals are really tiny, when they're babies,
they don't know and they just, they feel the energy and people.
Yeah.
Two.
Right.
I mean, it's like, because it's like they're babies and so it's like, it's all play.
It's not like, you know.
It's pure.
Yeah.
It's very, it's very, it's like, you know, as you put, even like, like when they say,
when they have babies of different races and stuff, there's no prejudice or racism
there until introduced by their parents, right?
True. Yeah, I think that it's it's basically like there's such an innocence about
Connecting with everybody and loving everybody at a certain point and then it's like you're told oh this person
There's all these differences. You don't learn. You don't learn hate racism
Colorism bigotry misogyny until
Right on it, you know or something really bad happens to you
And they're not natural things and so that's why I wonder like who introduced them into the human
Ideas because a lot of these are just ideas. Well, it's it's to keep us divided
It's on purpose
All right. Well, do you want to hear the whole song that I you know?
I I want you to hear the whole song. It's because I get it and I put a little slow motion
the end just now. Yeah, well, it's gonna be a project. I'm turning you into a
project. You're gonna, you're gonna, you're gonna get a kick out of it. Okay,
but this is just a mini mini mini teeny tiny preview, but I want you to have the
whole song. The song is based on George Michael because I'm big into George
Always a fan. All right. People's here saying hi to us too. Yeah, what's up? Great. Full. What's up girl?
Yeah, we're gonna wear dying
Alice's new video. Let's check it out
Nothing on TV
So I open YouTube
I've been watching the Badmoms live all day. Those Badmoms from the panel
verse aren't you like glowing. Go check it out.
Know your business. Your neighbors know your business. The whole internet knows your business.
Been watching the bad looking for another true drama. Fly.
I gotta pause it. I think this is the best version of you. I created it in the AI.
I like my butt, but I think I have a nice butt in this video.
Well, I wasn't looking at that part.
I was looking at the fit.
To me, this was, what do you think?
What do you think?
Yeah, that's my eyebrow.
That's your face
At least green cap that I'm gonna screen cap that for you right now
There you go. Cuz that's that's you that's that's you right there
Everything you told me about you know going to school for fashion not merchandising
to
Just who you are
To me. This is you. I want that I want that sweater or that jacket or whatever
We got it. We got to get you that jacket. Okay
Jacket. We're gonna have to find somebody who can print that fabric and make you that jacket. I'm sexy. Oh my gosh
You are let's I gotta get back to the beginning. I would be annoying with this cuz I'm drinking. I'm sorry
Yeah
So I love
This is you today, you know is not amplify. This is what you would look like
This is yet again
Nothing on TV
So I open you back in a week and there they were
Yes
And this is not a bad mom that's in the community, this is a fictitious bad mom, but she could be many of them
Think about it
Could be it could be BXO. It could be a young Trisha. It could be a lot of people
And look at that look to my own horn, but I got your height right
Right
Got your height right cuz you're very tall people don't know that about you. It's psyche is very tall. He's about six four
Okay, on a runway that's average, but you can see the comparison when it comes to the people backstage, okay?
That's you right there. That's you. Okay. Well, if you'd like to admit it or not there you are
And run away that mom, but where are you going to run to?
Huh?
There she is.
Yeah, looking at her kids, then spending too much time
on the internet, and you see what happens.
This show, but they never.
Your chat knows your business.
Your neighbors know your business.
The whole internet knows your business.
Been watching the badm.
Looking for another trend.
Oh, who do you know?
Yeah.
Okay.
Vidal says soon.
If you don't look good, I wouldn't look good on you.
I was taking care.
Can this last?
I ain't judging.
Okay, maybe a little.
But if the kids keep raising themselves,
somebody's gonna make a phone call.
That's it.
For situations like these somewhere,
you know the one.
Three little letters
The kids deserve more attention than the audience
The best thing ever is that the kids deserve more attention than the audience.
They do.
Well, I try to make everything with a good message.
Yeah, and I like that.
It's like, you know what?
It's like, you know, you can be a live streamer if you're even a bad mom or whatever,
but it's like, you got to love your kids first.
I mean, it's like, that's got to be like the number one.
Yeah, well, you've got to work on it.
I mean, let the chat help you become a good mom.
Why not?
And I think you're helping them become good moms too just even the recognition
Right.
It's like you know because a lot of people are like, you know, they don't even care about the kids
You know, they'll docks the kids so those I mean, so you care about you care about them as mothers and their children and stuff like that
Well, they don't realize it, but maybe you know on the other side somebody will inform them
Yeah, I hope they do I hope they do and I hope they get it because it's like you're not here to like
Trash people or I mean, I mean I'm just doing artistic projects at this point because I've tried so hard
With so many of them and it's been nothing but backstabbing heartbreak just
Right, whatever they can do to hurt me even though I tried to help and I'm just like I'm over it
But I am
Not gonna let them get away with it. I feel like all right. I at least want to make it known to your kids
That someone did try with your ass and that way when you're kid is looking at you like what happened
You cannot act like nobody tried to help
Right, and they don't get it, but you know I get it I get it and it's like and I think that their eyes will open
if they get the ego out of the way.
I know, not in this lifetime.
Yeah.
I know.
If you go the other way, in order to raise your kids in the best way, I mean, it really
is, it's like.
That's once you have kids. That's what it's about. It's not about all the nonsense
I mean, I don't I don't have children and so I can like fuck around on the internet and have fun
But it's like if I had kids I would not be on the internet fucking around like I really wouldn't that's why I don't understand
That's why you would
Maybe, I don't know what it would take, really.
Right, I mean, what you're doing is an eye-opener.
As an eye-opener is like, let me see myself
through somebody else's eyes, like, you know, let me see.
And I think you're doing really good work.
I think you're like,
You know and I but it's ultimately about your heart
It's like you do have a good heart like such a good heart about these people and it's like even they I know they've betrayed you a thousand times
And it's like and you you still will give them a chance. I don't want I don't want some of the
You know, I can't really speak for the mothers of the signs because I'm a girl and I don't know
What it would be like to be your mom. That's where I'm crippled
He's a girlfriend he's a girl or his wife
Hi, I'm good. How are you doing girly? Yeah. Good girl. I'm just like fucking sunburned today today
My fucking something ran over and I didn't know this how much some bird out good
But look at my forehead like where that's what well put some sunscreen with you have any aloe. I look like a fucking potato
Hey, I try to do all your lotion and everything you need some aloe aloe vera
Put that on your skin. Yeah, she's a really sweet. Look at it. Yeah
She has a personality like three or glow
I'm glad she came on because I'm not a fan of glow right now, but I'm sure the girl is nice
Yeah
Like him they can humanize people
Than you are glow. Yeah, I'm sorry. Hey, but glow. Okay. Hey, I like Sandra
I told her all about your big titties and she likes it. Okay. I don't have that big of titties
I don't I'm I'm kind of
Then he lighted me but oh yeah
Yeah, what are you doing you're drinking chashu chashu? What is going on here? What is the other drinking over there?
There's nothing going on here. Close your eyes psyche
Well, I'm glad he's drinking because that gives the girl an opportunity to dish out to him what he deserves
Yeah, I've ever peed the bed have you ever gotten so drunk you peed in the bed with her in it. I know guys like
Like I'll be like
My girl piece is there, but...
She pees? Oh my god, not you, Mrs. Glove.
Well, she gets too drunk, though.
Not like, oh, it's normalized.
Well, don't call us.
We don't...
Thank you. Chill out.
You're getting too horny now.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm gonna shut up. I'm gonna shut up.
No, I think...
What about Alexandra and Dina have a sex video?
Well, it would be the most popular sex video that I've probably ever made and unfortunately, I would not allow you to be a part of it
Will be the cameraman
And we're the only ones recording we can't even touch what are you gonna call the video we're gonna call the video
I'm gonna take your wife I'm gonna take her for myself. Fuck you. I've had enough
I'm going to take her for myself and we're going to travel the world and we're going to forget about you. Oh
shit
Now baby girl, I'll take you for myself and take you with myself with the world. That's right
We're done. You're out. You're out. It's all about me and mrs. Glow. Yep
You better be careful because you got you got competition. I will take your girl
Don't need the only reason you have competition is because of your tits. No, no for me
They ain't no competition. I will take you any time any second any minute
You've heard that she's ready to go you better be good to that girl
I mean, he just has to work at
the right way. If I could cover
your years, I'm going to cover
you. You have to come over here.
We're going to fish tacos and
fish here. Oh, yeah. I'm going
to kidnap. I'm going to kidnap
Mrs. Glow. I'm going to take her
with me on my travels. I'm going
to take her to Psyche's house.
Psyche's house.
I'm going to take her to visit other streamers and then I'll then at the end when she misses you
I'll bring her back home. She will miss you even fully
So I'll take her I'll take her back home. She'll have been a world traveler and you'll be jealous
forever
That's what happened
Oh, I'll take her for a month psyche stop checking off under the
Attorney read too fast. Well, he might be so what he's at home
You guys are so hot it doesn't matter as up freeze
Do you see the psyche music video?
Did you see the music video? Yeah, I was playing it when it came out. Yeah, watching the bat, mom.
That's just a movie.
We're watching the bat, moms.
Play it, play it, so I can play it, bro.
Yeah, let's play it again. How do I play it again?
Maybe worse. I got ten viewers.
Just put it back on there. Put it back on there.
Yeah.
Woo!
That's right!
Oh!
No!
That's right!
That's what he entertainment signals missing out
Your chat knows your business
Your neighbors know your business
The whole internet knows your business
That's a filter!
That's a filter, I think
No, that's you!
I don't know what you're talking about
Look at that flag right there
You'll make it look like you're taking it
How can this last?
I ain't judging
Tao, baby
But if the kids keep raising themselves
I think somebody's gonna make a phone call
GPS
Hey, it's just here, Bad Boy Breeze is in here
Bad Boy Breeze
Oh, Bad Boy Breeze
Music, we're having fun
Yeah, we're watching some fire on you
You're watching some fire
Yeah, the girls that full psyche is gay, so he's like the girls are stripping never mind
Psyche is probably gonna end up becoming the
on here wait wait I feel like we're doing the little x-rated the motorboat show come on she's hot
she's hot she is hot oh three inch and glow you better buy her a diamond ring buy her a diamond ring
I
Look at them kissing
Here's pretty hair
I know it is I know it is you have a beautiful head of hair girl
He probably takes care of his hair when I think about it
Yeah, I use her condition there. Yeah, that's why it's hot.
That's why I'm here. I look so good.
That's why I'm here. Look at it.
Did you see her hair? She has beautiful hair.
I saw it. Yeah, she has gray hair.
Yeah, she has beautiful hair.
You're the cutest couple.
I mean, I haven't seen her like that close, but I mean, I mean.
Hey, like Sandra, are you naked right now or what?
No, I'm wearing my clothes
Terrible right now what you want to see me. I'm a terrible
Decent lighting
I'm like a old lady because that's who I am
How old are you?
I'm a old lady. I'll turn my camera
I mean nobody
The dabs, they're dabbing each other, they're, oh, yeah, yeah, oh, shit.
I'm just like, brandy.
Where the fuck, where the fuck, where the fuck?
I have a little face, I look like a little weirdo.
I already know it.
No, I'm just showing you because I got fucking sunburn.
I'm like, where the fuck?
Let me show you a little bit better.
Hold up, I gotta show out a little bit.
I can't believe it.
Wow, wow, psyche 10.
Hold up.
I'm gonna be full screen, hold on a second.
I mean, from there's my phone.
Let me show out.
Ew, why not?
Cause I don't look that bad, come on, let's get it together, Alex, Alex, I'm sorry, what the fuck, what the fuck is wrong with me?
I gotta use the bathroom first, put your camera on there.
Okay, I mean look at 300 low full screen.
I gotta get ready.
Oh my god, your girlfriend's beautiful or oh my god
She's very pretty
Yeah
Oh god
You're like Quincy's in a sort of way
Hold on she was so hot the glue. I'm sorry. I got it. I was like you with like glasses
I don't know if you're building from
I'll cook up for everybody
I know
Birria tacos, asada tacos, chicken tacos, any fucking tacos, some red...
I'll cook up for everybody
Lele Sandra, Lele Sandra's... Lele Lele Sandra's...
Alright, yeah, let's see what happens.
Well, you gotta put on the bad mom's song again. Put that shit back on.
Put the bad song.
Put the song. I gotta be inspired to turn the hair around.
There's this girl right here.
How do you do it?
How do we do it?
There we go.
Ready?
Where am I?
Pick up the cheese.
Yeah!
I have to bring the cheese out.
Oh yeah, it's done.
Very well.
There's time out.
Yeah, baby.
Go.
Come back.
Go ahead.
That's the level.
You saw me. You saw me. You saw me. Okay.
I love you, girl.
I came out, I came out, my boo almost came out, because that's not right.
I'm drinking, I'm having my drinks, whatever am I supposed to do, you know?
You're gonna hurt yourself.
Yeah.
Watching the bad moms.
Have you fully respected and everything and fucking good?
Okay.
I just thought that somebody's gonna caress your body in the right way. It's not let me do this shit. I'm
Why am I the one to get raised what the fuck oh come on your globe get over here. I'm the nice guy
I know I want to run my hands
He's not a bad guy Alex. He's not a bad guy. He's actually I know he's not he's nice
He's got that
We have a good girl that means that you're a good guy great. I believe in my girl
Yeah
Let me take a sip of this babe, and you can have it yes
I think he's talking to me Alex
Me and Dina were at Venice Beach today. We went to go meet Paul Rodriguez. Piro. Oh
Did you what did you go to the muscle beat and look at the bottom? Yeah? Yeah?
Bro, I'm the biggest guy there. I'm the tallest guy there and it wasn't my only cat there
Bro, we got Power Rodriguez to sign my shirt on my kiddies dress everything
Well, who's that guy that who's that he's another Mexican guy. He's in all the Mexican movies
He's in that like he's in this like
It's like a satanic cult who's that guy do you know who I'm talking about he's like in like the animal
Lovers of Los Angeles, but it's like some kind of satanic cult.
Why do you know?
Paul Rodriguez signed my kid.
I'll find out.
There is something called that called the process the process is now like the animal lovers of Beverly Hills
I know if lovers are in it, but it used to be as a satanic cult in like the 70s 80s
That's your diet already psyche. Maybe it did but let me see the process
Doesn't want it to die. He he's bringing it back
The process
You know what I am if you don't mind
Pray for me. I am trying next year and my
She wants a little 300
May you have one
You've been together since after high school well
I hope you have one more than I do honestly if you've been together that long and that you want to have a baby
I hope that yeah husbands, and they never
Your god our father who are in heaven
Husbands you're god your god
No, I don't you know because they all
Help this couple have their dream
Girls wins all cheated on you. Um, I'm trying to pray for your girl. So why don't you shut the fuck up dumbass?
No, I'm gonna make sure you have a kid now. I pray that you have twins
your male twins grow up and look at their father
and they see this stream and they say,
dad, you were a dumbass talking to that woman that way.
And I hope that both those twins
kick the living hell out of you, girl.
I have so many people can see that it's ridiculous, but that's what's gonna happen to you
Because God has not blessed me with a trial, but I want you to have to kick your ass
Having kids is like we're ABT government. Yeah, that's what you think you're gonna have to a twins
Twins my brother's my brother's name. Hey
Ex-sander
It was an X. Well, then that's a that's a sign
Ex-sander. Yeah. No, you'll have to you'll get your children, but your children will grow up to be strong
They're gonna be two it's gonna be twins and those sons are gonna look at their father one day when he's acting stupid
Take your tits again or shut the fuck up
Shut the fuck up. Shake your teeth.
You shut the fuck up.
Shake your teeth.
Don't worry. I'll be, I'll be your kids' grand, I'll be your kids' godmother.
I am Alexander.
I will be, no, I already owe your ass.
I've already created your children.
I have created your voice, yes, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Why would you say that in front of your wife? I know you got ugly big
Get out of here. Yeah, yeah out of here. They're in glow you make it up to your wife right here. Oh, yeah, there we go
Oh, there you go. Well good
No, I love you guys. I love you. I've already done that. I don't need to. It's getting too crazy. I mean, it's gonna
Yeah, they're horny. No, they're horny. We're gonna have twins. They're gonna have twin boys, right?
I bet they will. They have some twins. Yeah, I mean, they're a cute couple.
I thought she'd be like some like, you know, but no, she's gorgeous. She's very pretty. She's a pretty girl
Yeah
Did you have a good day today? I mean my day was okay. No, I didn't I actually didn't have a good day
It's okay. Sorry, you know, I mean
I didn't get anything done. I wanted done this weekend
But I guess that wasn't meant to because I'm a little tired just from life
You know, I'm a perfectionist by nature, so I'm hard on myself.
Um, I'm alright.
You're too hard on yourself because you know what, you're like, you're just a blessing
to know.
I don't know.
I'm not.
To the west side of the country because I don't like where I am you got to get out here because we got to hang out again
No, I'm on my way. I'm not exactly disclosing where I am
for obvious reasons, but
You're gonna see me soon. Don't worry. I'd love to you. Yeah, I
Mean a little I mean probably getting too drunk, but I want to know I am you're too
Well, I just want to say I love you and thank you for like, you know always being
Like a breath of fresh air a ray of light everything that you are I mean it's a
That's what it comes down to it. We're and we're crazy on top of it
The song again, cuz I feel like dancing over here
At the beginning yeah
Cuz I it's it I feel funky. It's a funky song. Yeah, let's get the funky town. All right. Here we go. All right
So I open YouTube
Everybody
What I'm thinking about for the rest of the video is just making a fashion shoot about
you.
What do you think about that?
I'm down.
I think so.
I think, I think we should just make you the model, the model, because you are a model.
If you're over six feet, you have to be a model anyway, my mom has said
Mom's not AI photos of me. She's like, you're right. She's like, you're hot
She's like you gotta like get get a modeling company to like sponsor you or something and it's like yeah, I think I should
Well, my analysis, I'll be the model company. All right, there we go
Before we go, I want to show your latest video
Oh, so did you hear?
Well, not the latest but the other one the other one I'm using to reprogram my spirit a little bit here
Let me put that one up
Is it a new one?
No, no, no, there's another one. I mean hold on. Let me bring it up
It's a cartoony. It's kind of like a cartoon kind of thing more so let me bring it up. Let's see
I put it
Bad boy breeze bad way breeze. I like here. I like your um
your post bad bad boy raises some really funny posts where he talks about his life and how hard it is sometimes I
Just enjoy his post it. They're always pretty funny
Yeah, I know the bad boy raises. Yes. Yeah, make sure you subscribe to him everybody like cuz he's
Song real quick
I guess I put it somewhere else.
I'm drinking a thing, this thing's called prime.
I don't know if you've ever heard of this.
This is like, it's like battery.
No, what is it?
It's Logan Paul's drink and they're like,
we're gonna make it taste like a little obstacle.
It tastes like, you know, it tastes like you just drink
like a bottle of water with a whole thing of nicotine.
Yeah, I stick with the Pinot Noir, the hard spider,
and that's all I can take.
I'll call I can barely even drink when I'm drinking right now to be honest with you
Q lately, I mean a Q has been
Excuse the taking down channels. He's working with Crystal Ann and Trisha. I mean, I don't understand that's a mistake on I mean
There are so many people who are good people who try to take him under our wing and he's an asshole
That's what it really comes down to I come down to the reality of that if it isn't his genetics to me that way
He cannot help it. Right, but I'm not going to coddle or pass by somebody who's ungrateful
Unappreciative
who's mean-spirited. I think that he has a lot of talent. I think that he has a lot of charisma.
He has a great look. There are parts of him that I do like, but who he is right now, today, I don't
like who he is, and I'm ashamed to have ever been associated with him considering how he treats people. I don't like it.
Right
And and just because like someone requested this in chat before you find your video. This is another one you made
This is with cute cute
This is a class. I think this is a classic video before you get your other one
Oh, well wait till you see the full version. I already know what you're talking about and I haven't finished the full version yet
But you talking about the this one right here. Yeah, I know you're talking about okay. Go ahead right here
I think everyone wants to see this one right now
Oh, I'm sure they do
It's not worth it
to the streams to avoid thinking about my lost hopes and dreams i want to be a slave
fuck you even though i know he's associate
hey potz, i know you don't know what to do i don't want to be a slave
here you go
Do you notice how there's a little bit of a play on the words or the alliteration there when it says,
I want to be a slave for Q. It could also be translated to, I want to be a slave, fuck you.
Oh, there you go. Fuck. Can you notice that? You know, some people didn't notice it. I like that. I like that. There's like, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, grateful. She wants a full length. I haven't finished it yet. And I'm a perfectionist. You know how I am. So it's not ready yet. It's not ready because some more has to happen before I put it out there.
You know, when's that gonna happen?
I don't know, you tell me.
I mean.
I was telling INX, there's something called
the Mayor's Briggs system, which is like a personality test.
And I was like, I'm in the Mayor's Briggs system.
I've been, it's like, she probably thought
Alexander Mayor's, but I was like, as the Mayor's Briggs,
but I'm an INXP in that system.
And so, yeah, and so I,
You thought that that was what a man like INX, but she means I think it was the band INX or INX.
No, she likes INX. She called herself.
Yeah, so that was it. But I mean, it's funny how there's coincidences in this world and stuff.
Yeah, it is. It was not coincidences. It just is what it is.
No, here's my fun song. This is because I'm reprogramming myself. This is helping me
Regress my age a little bit
For a minute. Yeah, um, I was asking bad boy if he'll join us because he had he knows a lot about those two
Cuz you know, I mean we need to do a formal stream
It can't just be off the cuff if we're going to really
Because I know that you know y'all like to keep it casual, but I don't I want it to be formal
Yeah, yeah, it's trying to talk about it the right way
Right, okay, and then bad boy. That's what I was letting him know because I don't see him much though and
He's a good guy. He's really a good
He tells the truth and
And you know what I?
Suggested to iron next that we set up a solid day in time
To discuss what needs to be discussed formally because I don't want it to be to where it's just like off the cuff
We need to be serious about it, right?
Oh, he knows a lot like like about the Vienna situation I want him to be comfortable and I want him to when he's
Because I know he's got stuff going on. I've been reading the post so yeah
He stays busy, but he's so funny and he tells the truth too. He's he's he's been on panels before
Yeah
Yeah, come up and say hi and stuff like that. You're welcome here
I just appreciate you coming in the chat and stuff and hey, let's watch this that this is a new Alexander mayors video
I think okay. Well, I'm gonna jump off
Yeah, I had a busy day today
And I'm happy though Alex my my bully cat is accepting the boy cat now. They were just hanging out
you know and it's hard the last couple of weeks and she's just finally
well sometimes the cats will be bullies
She is a bully. It's like she just gets jealous, but something changed today because they got quiet and I looked at that
Oh, I hope she's not gonna screw with him and they were together. It was like wow by themselves
By the friend more you know because it's going to go out. Yeah, so I'm happy
So, okay, well, I'm gonna watch I'm gonna drop down and I'm gonna watch the video
I love your videos Alex and and watch my video
tagged you in
my post and uh and i'm glad jamie finally commented you know because
right first of all started a lot between us and and i just impressed her for so long and then
i remembered she was the one that helped me with the court thing against that person so because
she knew a lot so i appreciate that so okay so i'll watch you guys and uh and i'm gonna drop off
okay love you both okay okay have a good night have a good night here you go this is colorful i
Yeah, you'll like the song see
You love it
Cartoon me
All I'm gonna say is to the men out there who might want to romance me
All you have to say to me is hey bitch you look 27 to me
You want to see something I have all right hold on just give me a second and I'll show it
something new when it comes to, because well your audience might not know you
know that I'm a natural minimum, well not natural, I forced myself to be but a
minimalist and I have, remember that keyboard that it's been so cumbersome to
me and so heavy, it's been ridiculous. I finally replaced it for travel.
and I want to show you what I have now.
Let me turn my camera on.
Oh!
Well, yeah, but you haven't seen the best part.
Okay.
Watch this.
I have, I now don't have to lug around something over 100 pounds.
Oh
I didn't even know they made this
So now I have a full-size is 88 keys
Here, let me say it's 88
88 keys, but it's portable and I don't have to
Kill myself anymore
To carry it it splits
You go like that
Look at that. I never see anything like this
I've never seen you know I
Well, it was I wanted you know, your friend Alisa has the keytar
But I don't I didn't want to get a keytar, but this and it's some Bluetooth enabled
Okay, and it does everything
It's just like my old one and I did put a bunch of decals on it because you know, I'm 80s for all in a lot of ways
but
Yeah, it's very I had to I had to get it before I really started my next leg of travel, but now I'm ready
Yeah, and you got to play that
You'll be welcome anywhere with it listen to the piano like you're welcome anywhere really I mean it's like you pull it pretty much
Yeah, it's a good opening for you know people who want to get to know you and that's the reason might not happen tonight
But it's like I do appreciate you trying and it's like you'll come on soon
I think you come on soon and then come on the panel soon. I know he's having trouble problems of the streaming art
But not tonight's not meant for him to come on not not tonight
It needs to be we need to prepare in a way for a few things
And I want to thank Alexander tonight I want to thank everybody that's been in the chat
It's it's only 10 21 Los Angeles, but I am like, you know, I get a little bit drunk and then I like I'm kind of useless
Okay
But I love you Alexandra and yeah, and so yeah, and so a bad boy come join as soon as you can
Grateful, I want you to post you can post anywhere you can about Europe but that new live you're gonna do
I want to see yeah before joining. Yeah, you know, it's just a little bit of work, but thank you so much
Alexandra, thank you a grateful. Thank you bad boy breeze. Thank you. Who else is the charisma? Thank you even
I don't know. I'll do it here earlier too
You know there's something I think he threw it glow in his wife. I hope you have some great sex tonight
I hope you hope you can see they are going to get it on tonight, man
That was I felt like they were trying to like bring us into their sex life tonight
Intimate it was intimate when I saw the motor boating going on. Yeah
We were a part of it. We were somehow in there. We didn't mean to be but we were
We got a little I think we
In a verbally got some hit-and-run sex. I know it was it was good. I mean I had to turn it off before I got to
I know I got I got a little excited
Other because I mean, you know, I'm in the Mexican. I didn't expect that I didn't expect the sexiness
That's like that but that's what the Latin, you know, it's like Latin. It's the latinas the latinos
It's like it's like human bodies of hot sauce or something like that. They're just yeah
and we and sometimes
With the sexiness happens, and you don't even know it's it's fair. You're like you think everything's normal and then all of a sudden
you're hit with
a little sexiness.
And you're like, huh?
I got some hot sauce in my face watching them.
And so thank you for, thank you guys.
You got to inspire me.
But yeah.
I feel like I have like some really hot salsa.
Yeah, so it's also like that like the the the spiciest pepper in there that you can get in there all sliced up really
Yeah, really fine. You got some habanero or goes. Yeah
They seem to want to bring people into their relationships. I don't know why
Like why why do they do that? I don't know
Okay, I feel like I was a part of something
Turn off the camera. Everything we're going to be just saying is that we don't want to be just forced to do that.
Yeah, we're ready. We're here.
Oh, my gosh. Well, thank you guys. I mean, I'm about to pass out, but thank you so much, Alex
Thank you the chat and everything. I haven't I'm selling fun doing this show in 535 people. There's 50 people
Hey, it's so much is as much fun for me, and I love you guys. Thank you for being here everybody
And I hope you have a happy rest of the day rest of the night. So you're going to bed. Okay?
I'm falling asleep. I mean, I don't want to fall asleep on anybody because it's like
Okay, I love you. I love you. I love you sweetheart and thank you all right well
Bye
Bye sweetheart. I'll see you soon. Okay. You're fun. Okay. Have a good night
Bye guys. Bye guys. Have a good night guys. I love you